A Guide to the Sealantic Fund Records FA265
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 191)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 192)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 193)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 194)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1966-1969 (Box 37, Folder 195)
- Nursing Program: New York University- Department of Nursing Education, 1958-1967 (Box 38, Folder 196)
- Nursing Program: University of North Carolina- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 197)
- Nursing Program: Northeastern University, 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 198)
- Nursing Program: Ohio State University- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 199)
- Nursing Program: University of Pittsburgh, 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 200)
- Nursing Program: University of Pittsburgh, 1958-1964 (Box 38, Folder 201)
- Nursing Program: University of Portland, 1965-1969 (Box 39, Folder 202)
- Nursing Program: University of Pennsylvania- School of Nursing, 1958-1964 (Box 39, Folder 203)
- Nursing Program: Rutgers University- College of Nursing, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 204)
- Nursing Program: St. Johns University- Department of Nursing Education, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 205)
- Nursing Program: Sealantic Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 206)
- Nursing Program: Skidmore College, 1965-1971 (Box 39, Folder 207)
- Nursing Program: Seattle University- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 208)
- Nursing Program: Seton Hall University- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 209)
- Nursing Program: Catherine Spalding College, 1966-1970 (Box 39, Folder 210)
- Nursing Program: Texas Christian University- Harris College of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 211)
- Nursing Program: University of Texas- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 212)
- Nursing Program: University of Utah- College of Nursing, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 213)
- Nursing Program: Vanderbilt University- School of Nursing, 1959-1971 (Box 39, Folder 214)
- Nursing Program: Wagner College, 1967-1970 (Box 39, Folder 215)
- Nursing Program: University of Washington- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 216)
- Nursing Program: Wayne State University- College of Nursing, 1958-1966 (Box 40, Folder 217)
- Nursing Program: Western Reserve University- Frances Payne Bolton School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 218)
- Miscellaneous: NU-NZ, 1962-1973 (Box 40, Folder 219)
- Miscellaneous: O, 1955-1973 (Box 40, Folder 220)
- Palisades Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 221)
- Palisades Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 222)
- Palisades Fund, December 1962 (Box 41, Folder 223)
- Palisades Fund, August-November 1962 (Box 41, Folder 224)
- Palisades Fund, 1957-December 1962 (Box 41, Folder 225)
- Palisades Fund, October- April 1956 (Box 41, Folder 226)
- Palisades Fund, January-March 1956 (Box 41, Folder 227)
- Palisades Fund, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 228)
- Palisades Fund, 1952-1954 (Box 42, Folder 229)
- Palisades Fund: Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 42, Folder 230)
- Miscellaneous: PA, 1955-1972 (Box 42, Folder 231)
- Miscellaneous: PB-PH, 1955-1969 (Box 42, Folder 232)
- Pittsburgh Theological Seminary, 1955-1969 (Box 43, Folder 233)
- Miscellaneous: PI, 1964-1971 (Box 43, Folder 234)
- Miscellaneous: PJ-PQ, Undated (Box 43, Folder 235)
- Princeton Theological Seminary, 1955-1971 (Box 43, Folder 236)
- Princeton Theological Seminary, Undated (Box 43, Folder 237)
- Project Test Patterns, 1971-1973 (Box 43, Folder 238)
- Miscellaneous: PR, 1955-1973 (Box 43, Folder 239)
- Miscellaneous: PS-REG, 1955-1973 (Box 44, Folder 240)
- Rehearsal Club, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 241)
- Rehearsal Club, 1969-1972 (Box 44, Folder 242)
- Rehearsal Club, 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 243)
- Rehearsal Club, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 244)
- Rehearsal Club, 1962-1965 (Box 45, Folder 245)
- Rehearsal Club, 1958-1961 (Box 45, Folder 246)
- Rehearsal Club, 1956-1958 (Box 45, Folder 247)
- Rehearsal Club, 1954-1956 (Box 46, Folder 248)
- Rehearsal Club, 1949-1954 (Box 46, Folder 249)
- Rehearsal Club, 1941-1948 (Box 46, Folder 250)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 468 Riverside Drive, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 251)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 468 Riverside Drive, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 252)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 468 Riverside Drive, 1958-1962 (Box 47, Folder 253)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 468 Riverside Drive- Apartment 53, 1961-1965 (Box 47, Folder 254)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 49 Claremont Avenue, 1958-1968 (Box 48, Folder 255)
- Riverside Drive Property Fund: 49 Claremont Avenue- Insurance, 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 256)
- Miscellaneous: REH-RIU, 1955-1971 (Box 49, Folder 257)
- Miscellaneous: RIV-RIU, 1955-1972 (Box 49, Folder 258)
- Miscellaneous: SA-SD, 1955-1973 (Box 49, Folder 259)
- Miscellaneous: SE-SI, 1955-197 (Box 49, Folder 260)
- Miscellaneous: SJ-SN, 1955-1973 (Box 49, Folder 261)
- Sealantic Fund: Certificate of Incorporation and Bylaws, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 262)
- Sleepy Hollow Fund: Old Dutch Church, 1958-1958 (Box 50, Folder 263)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Closing Papers, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 264)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Correspondence and Payments, Undated (Box 50, Folder 265)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, 1950-1952 (Box 50, Folder 266)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 267)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Historical Society of the Tarrytowns- Society's New Headquarters, 1950-1953 (Box 51, Folder 268)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Record of the Distribution of The Old Dutch Burying Ground of Sleepy Hollow, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 269)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Report on the Distribution of The Old Dutch Burying Ground of Sleepy Hollow, 1957-1958 (Box 51, Folder 270)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Sealantic Fund and Historical Society Correspondence- Philipse Castle Restoration, 1950-1952 (Box 51, Folder 271)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations: Sealantic Fund and Historical Society Correspondence- Philipse Castle Restoration, 1948-1949 (Box 52, Folder 272)
- Miscellaneous: SO-SOUTHERN B, 1955-1973 (Box 52, Folder 273)
- Miscellaneous: SOUTHERN C-SOZ, 1955-1973 (Box 52, Folder 274)
- Miscellaneous: SP-ST, 1955-1973 (Box 52, Folder 275)
- Study of Restoration Projects Fund, 1948-1957 (Box 52, Folder 276)
- Sunnyside Administrative Workbook (AWP), 1943-1948 (Box 53, Folder 277)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Blanket Position Bond, 1948-1952 (Box 53, Folder 278)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Fine Arts Insurance, 1946-1952 (Box 53, Folder 279)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Fire Insurance, 1947-1952 (Box 53, Folder 280)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Messenger and Interior Robbery, 1950-1952 (Box 53, Folder 281)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Miscellaneous, 1945-1952 (Box 53, Folder 282)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Owners and Contractors Protective Public Liability, 1946-1948 (Box 54, Folder 283)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Owners, Landlords, and Tenants Public Property Liability, 1947-1952 (Box 54, Folder 284)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Steam Boiler, 1945-1952 (Box 54, Folder 285)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Insurance- Workmen's Compensation, 1946-1952 (Box 54, Folder 286)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Inventories, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 287)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Inventories- Appraised Inventories, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 288)
- Sunnyside & Philipse Castle: Photographs and Motion Pictures, 1948-1950 (Box 55, Folder 289)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Correspondence- Operating Account, 1948-1951 (Box 56, Folder 290)
  Upon RBF request, this material is closed from scholarly access.
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Correspondence and Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 56, Folder 291)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: General, 1945-1951 (Box 56, Folder 292)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Operating Account, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 293)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Reports- Operating Account, 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 294)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Reports- Operating Account, 1950-1952 (Box 57, Folder 295)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Reports- Monthly Activities of Philipse Castle and Sunnyside, 1946-1950 (Box 57, Folder 296)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Reports- Publications and Restoration Accounts, 1948-1952 (Box 58, Folder 297)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Restoration Fund, 1947-1948 (Box 58, Folder 298)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Restoration Operating Account, 1948-1950 (Box 58, Folder 299)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Sunnyside Fund, 1945-1948 (Box 58, Folder 300)
- Sunnyside & Philpse Castle Special Accounts: Sealantic Fund Special Account, 1946-1948 (Box 58, Folder 301)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 59, Folder 302)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 303)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 304)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 305)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports: Correspondence, 1950-1051 (Box 60, Folder 306)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 307)
- Sunnyside Agent Account Reports: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 308)
- Sunnyside Agent Account: H.G Rowell Account- Changed 1948 to Sunnyside Agent Account, 1945-1948 (Box 61, Folder 309)
- Sunnyside Lane, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 310)
- Sunnyside Purchase, 1945-1949 (Box 62, Folder 311)
- Miscellaneous: SU-SZ, 1955-1970 (Box 63, Folder 312)
- Miscellaneous: T-TG, 1955-1972 (Box 63, Folder 313)
- Miscellaneous: TH-THEOLOGICAL EDUCATION T, 1955-1978 (Box 63, Folder 314)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1970-1974 (Box 63, Folder 315)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 316)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 317)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 318)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 319)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 320)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1960-1966 (Box 65, Folder 321)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools, 1955-1959 (Box 66, Folder 322)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- American Theological Library Association, 1971-1973 (Box 66, Folder 323)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- American Theological Library Association, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 324)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- American Theological Library Association, 1955-1963 (Box 66, Folder 325)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- ALTA Library Development Program, 1966-1973 (Box 67, Folder 326)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- ALTA Library Development Program, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 327)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- ALTA Library Development Program, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 328)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- ALTA Library Development Program, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 329)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- ALTA Library Development Program, 1958-1960 (Box 68, Folder 330)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 331)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 332)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 333)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 334)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 335)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Case Study Institute, 1965-1970 (Box 70, Folder 336)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Cresap Study, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 337)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Cresap Study, 1959-1961 (Box 70, Folder 338)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Evanston Theological Center, 1972-1973 (Box 70, Folder 339)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Faculty Fellowship Program, 1964-1972 (Box 70, Folder 340)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Faculty Fellowship Program, 1956-1963 (Box 70, Folder 341)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools Fund, 1958-1960 (Box 71, Folder 342)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools Fund, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 343)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools Fund- Protestant Fellowship Fund, 1955-1960 (Box 71, Folder 344)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Monthly Staff Reports, 1959-1966 (Box 71, Folder 345)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: American Association of Theological Schools- Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 71, Folder 346)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Board of Missions of the United Methodist Church, 1968-1970 (Box 71, Folder 347)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Boston Theological Institute (formerly Cabal), 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 348)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Boston Theological Institute (formerly Cabal), 1971 (Box 72, Folder 349)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Boston Theological Institute (formerly Cabal), 1970 (Box 72, Folder 350)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Boston Theological Institute (formerly Cabal), 1969 (Box 72, Folder 351)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Boston Theological Institute (formerly Cabal), 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 352)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: University of Chicago, 1961-1969 (Box 73, Folder 353)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: University of Chicago, 1956-1960 (Box 73, Folder 354)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: University of Chicago, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 355)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Colgate Rochester Divinity School, 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 356)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Colgate Rochester Divinity School, 1956-1968 (Box 74, Folder 357)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Conference on Theological Education- Preparatory Papers, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 358)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Conference on Theological Education, 19-31 March 1963 (Box 75, Folder 359)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Conference on Theological Education, 1962-1966 (Box 75, Folder 360)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Episcopal Theological School, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 361)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Episcopal Theological School, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 362)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Episcopal Theological School, 1963-1966 (Box 76, Folder 363)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Episcopal Theological School- Conference on Case Method in Theological Education, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 364)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Episcopal Theological School- Conference on Case Method in Theological Education, 13 May 1967 (Box 76, Folder 365)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fact Book on Theological Education, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 366)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education, 1968-1974 (Box 76, Folder 367)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 368)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 369)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education, 1964-1966 (Box 77, Folder 370)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education, 1960-1963 (Box 77, Folder 371)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Black Doctorial Candidates in Religion, 1968-1973 (Box 77, Folder 372)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Parish Ministries Fellowship Program, 1971-1973 (Box 78, Folder 373)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Parish Ministries Fellowship Program, 1968-1970 (Box 78, Folder 374)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Protestant Fellowship Program, 1969-1973 (Box 78, Folder 375)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Protestant Fellowship Program, 1964-1968 (Box 78, Folder 376)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Fund for Theological Education- Protestant Fellowship Program, 1960-1969 (Box 79, Folder 377)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: YA Dissertation Copies Info Sheet, Undated (Box 79, Folder 378)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Institute of Theology, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 379)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, 1970-1973 (Box 79, Folder 380)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 381)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 382)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 383)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, April-December 1966 (Box 80, Folder 384)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, January-March 1966 (Box 80, Folder 385)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, October-December 1965 (Box 81, Folder 386)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, September 1965 (Box 81, Folder 387)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, January-August 1965 (Box 81, Folder 388)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, May-December 1964 (Box 81, Folder 389)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, January-April 1964 (Box 82, Folder 390)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Graduate Theological Union, 1958-1962 (Box 82, Folder 391)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1970-1973 (Box 82, Folder 392)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 393)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 394)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1963-1966 (Box 83, Folder 395)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1956-1962 (Box 83, Folder 396)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Harvard Divinity School, 1952-1955 (Box 83, Folder 397)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Institute for Advanced Pastorial Studies, 1968-1972 (Box 83, Folder 398)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Institute for Advanced Pastoral Studies, 1957-1967 (Box 83, Folder 399)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 400)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 401)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 402)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, May-December 1969 (Box 84, Folder 403)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, January-April 1969 (Box 85, Folder 404)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 405)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1964-1967 (Box 85, Folder 406)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 407)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 408)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center Yearbook, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 409)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1960-1961 (Box 86, Folder 410)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 411)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1958 (Box 87, Folder 412)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Interdenominational Theological Center, 1955-1957 (Box 88, Folder 413)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Luther Theological Seminary, 1969-1973 (Box 88, Folder 414)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 415)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: New York Theological Seminary, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 416)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: New York Theological Seminary (formerly Biblical Seminary in New York), 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 417)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: New York Theological Seminary (formerly Biblical Seminary in New York), 1955-1969 (Box 88, Folder 418)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Pacific School of Religion, 1955-1973 (Box 89, Folder 419)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Press Releases, 1955-1956 (Box 89, Folder 420)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Probation Research, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 421)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Probation Research, 1965-1966 (Box 89, Folder 422)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: San Francisco Theological Seminary, 1961-1970 (Box 89, Folder 423)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary, 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 424)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary, 1966-1970 (Box 90, Folder 425)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary, 1965-1972 (Box 90, Folder 426)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary, 1958-1965 (Box 90, Folder 427)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary, 1952-1957 (Box 91, Folder 428)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Union Theological Seminary- Council for Financial Aid to Theological Education, 1962-1971 (Box 91, Folder 429)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, 1969-1972 (Box 91, Folder 430)